[
    { "prompt": "DILLBBTFTY?", "answer": "Do I look like boo boo the fool to you", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "JJJD", "answer": "Ju Ju J Dalaz", "category": "person" },
    { "prompt": "FYF", "answer": "Fix your face", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "ANSY", "answer": "Ain't nobody studying you", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "WYTYTT", "answer": "Who you think you talkin to", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "NTMNTMNTM", "answer": "Never too much never too much never too much", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "ROATSH", "answer": "Reach out and touch somebody's hand", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "YTHTBE?", "answer": "You told Harpo to beat me?", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "YGEYC?", "answer": "You gon eat yo cornbread", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "TBG", "answer": "That boy good! Coming to America", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "STTYN,ASN", "answer": "Somebody turn to your neighbor and say neighbor", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "YJUAYWGBD", "answer": "You jump up and you will get beat down", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "TATLITPWSG", "answer": "TO ALL THE LADIES IN THE PLACE WITH STYLIN GRACE, BIGGIE", "category": "lyrics" },
    { "prompt": "IIWI?LMWIIPMTDFIARI", "answer": "IS IT WORTH IT LET ME WORK IT I PUT MY THANG DOWN FLIP IT AND REVERSE IT", "category": "lyrics" },
    { "prompt": "IGSWIMKICHS", "answer": "I get so weak in my knees I can hardly speak", "category": "lyrics" },
    { "prompt": "IIABJTALTRR!", "answer": "It's in a book, just take a look the reading rainbow!", "category": "lyrics" },
    { "prompt": "GYLGWYBTAU!", "answer": "Girl ya look good won't you back that ass up. Juvenile", "category": "lyrics" },
    { "prompt": "YGDWBFY", "answer": "You gotta do what's best for you", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "YLJLYM", "answer": "You look just like your mom", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "YCFM", "answer": "You could've fooled me", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "ANGTFT", "answer": "Ain't nobody got time for that", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "YMLMGI", "answer": "Your my latest my greatest inspiration...Teddy P", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "INOUGSIO", "answer": "It's not over until god says it's over", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "YGMM?", "answer": "You got McDonald's money?", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "WWGITSDTN", "answer": "When we get in this store don't touch nothin", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "OOSOOM", "answer": "Out of sight out of mind", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "YFCN", "answer": "Your fav could never", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "IBAHF", "answer": "I'm blessed and highly favored", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "TMHTD", "answer": "Teach me how to dougie", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "TIWISLWDC", "answer": "This is what it sounds like when doves cry", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "BILG", "answer": "Before I let go..Frankie Beverly", "category": "song" },
    { "prompt": "SILIBAIP", "answer": "Say it loud I'm black and I'm proud", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "GIGATTATTGIG", "answer": "God is good all the time, all the time god is good", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "AUITKADKTF", "answer": "All up in the kool-aid and don't know the flavor", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "YCGTH", "answer": "You can get these hands", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "GYKIIILY", "answer": "Girl you know I I I love you", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "HWMUTMSMOMW", "answer": "He woke me up this morning started me on my way. Famous bible phrase", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "GYBAITGDHRNBIBYMFA", "answer": "Get yo black ass in the goddam house right now befor I beat your m f ass", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "YLJLYDD", "answer": "You look just like yo damn daddy", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "YESYAIOO", "answer": "You either stay yo ass inside or out", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "IDFWY", "answer": "I don't f*** wot you", "category": "phrase" },
    { "prompt": "FYF", "answer": "Fix your face", "category": "phrase" }
]

